[Music]
[Música]
what buttons do I have to use use the
qué botones tengo que usar usar los
buttons open the buttons what buttons
botones abrir los botones qué botones
what buttons
qué botones
and what were vests what buttons
y que fueron chalecos que botones
leave me alone and from entries
dejarme en paz y de entradas
preparing the thumbnails that today I don't
preparándome las miniaturas que hoy no
see myself this afternoon
me vea esta tarde
like Hayden doesn't have the thumbnails I'm not
como hayden no tenga las miniaturas no
going to upload the extracts below I said to
voy a subir los estractos abajo decía
remove vetoes now with the one we
quitar vetos ahora con el que nosotros
want to remove in ass [ __ ] him we'll
quiero quitar en por culo
make videos of those not of
ya haremos vídeos de esos no de
requests to remove this and take us
solicitudes de quitarme esto y llevarnos
through time when I have many they haven't just
por el tiempo cuando tenga muchas no
sent one they just sent
acaban de enviar una acaban de enviar
a bondi scholarship let's see if it's sure that it will
una beca bondi a ver si lo seguro que
be some some joke not
será alguna alguna broma no
a minute ago
hace un minuto
this was the fool from the other day
a este fue el tonto del otro día
who was telling me that in grace the ball to
que me decía que en gracia la pelota a
others youtube you ate
otros youtube te comiste un baneo a mí
a ban you don't know how sorry I am he is going through a complicated moment and I was not with h panama the witness of panama the tenths of the years [ __ ] you or rather the ban is not removed once they leave whether on youtube whether on youtube or here in
en youtube ya sea en youtube o aquí en
tweets
tweets
nothing is removed from the ban of anyone I don't know if it's
no se quita nada de baneo a nadie no se
a mistake  really
que sea un error de verdad
okay
vale
no one can take it away from me I
no se le quita a nadie
have it very clear this channel is going to
lo tengo ya muy clarito este canal va a
be a salt channel had a very healthy operation you
ser un canal de sal se operó muy sano te
like you read the ceo good vibes here you
igual que te lees al ceo buen rollo aquí
come to have a good time fun
se viene a pasar un buen rato divertido
no toxicity but not with the
nada de toxicidad pero ni con los
protagonists of the video or with anyone
protagonistas del vídeo ni con nadie
absolutely no one is worth it and nothing is
absolutamente nadie vale y no se
allowed time that is
permiten nada vez que sean falta de
disrespectful absolutely none okay if you
respeto absolutamente ninguna vale si
want toxicity and fuss then go for it that's what I
queréis toxicidad y jaleo pues vais por
was telling myself whatever
el tocar es lo que me estaba diciendo lo
okay
que sea vale
here a little good vibes have a
aquí un poquito de buen rollo pasarlo
good time and a little more air you
bien y poco más aire
are here air there is that it
estás aquí aire
is here
hay de que está aquí
that it cannot verify its numbers
que no puede verificar sus números
because
porque
ah it
ah
is put in the tweet chat that they
es puesto en el chat de tweets que
have to verify their number and
tengan que verificar su número y el
email to be able to chat
email para poder chatear
and the car his mother has not verified
y el coche su madre no tiene verificado
the last number verify it she
el número último verificarlo
censored me I have been waiting for ten minutes for
me ha censurado llevo diez minutos
the code to what pauleta another
esperando el código a que pauleta otro
fact that I have done has been better
hecho que he hecho ha sido mejor
there is when you want
hay de cuando tú quieras
verifying the number when you want you
verificando el número cuando tú quieras
do the over ley no that also
me haces el over ley no eso también lo
has to do tina
tiene que hacer tina
here so that this can be seen cool I can
aquí para que se vea esto guay lo puedo
put a full screen I am in hand
poner un pantalla completo estoy de mano
what I have is here watching it  so
lo que tengo está aquí viéndolo así
I'm covering the dog
estoy tapando el perrito
when your mother
cuando tu madre
today I'm going to teach drawing that teaches me
hoy voy a enseñar dibujo que me enseña
to see the drawing I suck you
a ver el dibujo me sotina
have to be fair and you have to say that the
hay que ser justo y hay que decir que el
sketch not because she doesn't spend the tri
boceto no porque ella no se pase el tri
to belittle her or anything
por menospreciar la ni nada
javi hit present but if I hit
javi darle a presentar pero que si le
present it goes to
doy a presentar se pone en pantalla
full screen and you can't see it because you haven't
completa y no se ve porque no me habéis
made the overlay so I can put it
hecho el overlay para yo poder ponerlo
in full screen with chitu mother
en pantalla completa con chitu madre
and it will let you move the tab like tour
y te dejará mover la pestaña como tour
to finish it will be the people of the drawing I
para terminar será la gente del dibujo
don't have we shook hands I'm not going to
no tengo dimos la mano no lo voy a
show it let's see what I hit presentation
enseñar a ver que le dé a presentación
presentation and let me move the
presentación y que me deje mover la
tab of tab that is not sold the
pestaña de pestaña que no se vende los
days
días
that what I want is an overlay
que yo lo que quiere es un overlay
that looks more or less like this here
que quede esto más o menos así aquí
here okay
aquí vale
in fact look I'm going to do it
de hecho mira lo voy a hacer me voy a
I'm going to be an overlay right now there den
ser yo un overlay ahora mismo hay den
because you are really incompetent
porque sois unos incompetentes de verdad
oh by the way you know what and I say that
ah por cierto sabéis que y lo digo que
hire a kid to take
contrata a un chaval para que me lleve
the title for me and to do the titles for me
el título y para que me haga los títulos
since another thing gave us second
ya que otra cosa dio darnos segundo
I have hired a kid to
he contratado a un chaval para que me
take the red wine for me
lleve el tinto
and for me  make two christs a day
y para que me haga dos cristos al día
god
dios
because really it's that you're already alonso
porque de verdad es que ya estás alonso
valero or rather the title has to be
valero o sea el título tiene que
lamentable no matter or [ __ ]
lamentable no sea o [__]
beige eye I've been
ojo beige
saying for two months that you see my
llevo dos meses diciendo que me veis el
red wine gave I've
tinto dio
been telling me for two months to take the
llevo dos meses diciéndome llevarme el
[ __ ] uncle
[__] tito
take the [ __ ] uncle uncle
llevarme el [__] tito tío
saltito has to have two videos a
saltito tiene que tener dos vídeos al
day whether it's about lordship or kids
día ya sea de señoría o de chavalería
man two points videos a day and those two
tío dos puntos vídeos al día y esos dos
videos well I'll upload them here too like
vídeos pues yo lo subo también aquí como
georg
georg
and they'll get all of it
y ya se les sacará todo él
men people
hombres gente
if you take out the piggy bank well it's
si tú te sacas el cerdito pues va
growing and you want it not it's
creciendo y quieres que no es
a good move also for the channel to
un buen movimiento también para el canal
know but nothing guys we're busy
saber pero nada tíos estamos ocupados
paulo and I couldn't do it look man do you
paulo y no me lo podía hacer mira tío
see this
veis esto
this is one of my drawings of the new
este es uno de mis dibujos de los nuevos
designs that we're preparing for the
diseños que estamos preparando para la
new image that it's going to have now this is
nueva imagen que va a tener ahora esto
already the overdrive sucks you're no longer
ya está el overdrive chupa ya no tienes
successful paulo it
éxito paulo
's already god I don't
ya está dios
need you anymore paulo
ya no te necesito paulo
nor air so that so that you can me
ni aire para que para que me puedas
dog here it is
perro aquí
this is what I wanted air
ya está esto es lo que quería aire
I want several screens to have a
quiero varias pantallas para tener una
full screen another one on the left another one
pantalla completa otro la izquierda otro
on the right but oh well  moment we
a la derecha pero bueno de momento nos
leave like this
dejamos así
good for gales there is man air air
a buenos para galés hay de hombre aire
collects the one who does not charge is Paulo
aire cobra el que no cobra es paulo
so that he speaks because he is going to charge
para que hable porque va a cobrar
but it is because Paulo has to charge it
pero es que porque tiene que cobrar
is that I do not understand why Pau has to
es que no entiendo el porqué pau le
charge well we have 8
tiene que cobrar bueno llevamos 8
minutes of extract I think that in order not to
minutos de extracto yo creo que para no
anger the people who see the extracts it
cabrear a la gente que ve los extractos
would be good
estaría bien
that they [ __ ] each other also
que se jodan también
talking about the subject of the video arroyo
hablando del tema del vídeo arroyito
furious with the haters
furiosa con los haters
very important fundamental
importantísimo fundamental
[Music]
[Música]
not
no
exactly this has been this will have been
precisamente este ha sido este habrá
Paula's only contribution to the
sido el único aporte de paula en el
script
guión
okay air
vale aire
I'm going to verify this God
me voy a verificar esto dios
verify the autumn
verifica el otoño
or whatever regrettable regrettable
o sea lamentable
regrettable that this has been the only
lamentable que éste haya sido el único
contribution that the car her mother will have made the
aporte que habrá hecho el coche su madre
whole live and of until and that's it
todo el directo y de hasta y ya está
surely of all the rest of the
seguramente de todo el resto de los
scripts that we are going to see and what to love
guiones que vamos a ver y lo que amar
more than justified the salary and we
más que justificado el sueldo y nos
go really be literal man two
vamos de verdad sea literal tío dos
months I had to call a chip
meses he tenido que llamar a un chip
hired today a good kid
contratado hoy a un chaval bueno
hired
contratado
you go to a kid so that he makes me uncle I
vas a un chaval para que me haga tito yo
have said a month two red wines a day come on he
he dicho al mes dos tintos al día vamos
offered l
ha ofrecido l
heard me yesterday and  I sent an email and I
me escuchó ayer y mandó un email y le
told him to see signs more or less the
dicho a ver señales más o menos los
reds and continue the content and everything from
tintos y sigue el contenido y demás de
the lordship because I will have to say more or
la señoría porque tendré que decir más o
less what I want from the increase but even if
menos lo que quiero de suba pero aunque
I go up to two reds a day he gave two
me suba a dos tintos al día dio dos
funny ones look here there are one hundred thousand there are
chistosos mira aquí hay hay de cien mil
some who have one hundred thousand others who
hay algunos que tienen cien mil otros
have twenty thousand almost all have
que tienen veinte mil casi todos tienen
twenty thousand or around there man
veinte mil o por ahí tío
80000 look with this advertising for the
80000 mira con esta publicidad para los
channels
canales
with your mother
con tu madre
conchi your mother
conchi tu madre
the one with 100,000 it's not thanks to you the one with
el de 100.000 no es gracias a ti el de
100 thousand but I had to say seven times to
100 mil pero tuve que decir siete veces
do it paulo
que lo hiciera paulo
seven times the one with one hundred thousand so that you
siete veces el de cien mil para que lo
would do it
hicieras
and already the last thing because I have raised it and
y ya lo último porque lo he subido yo
you look man
y a vos mira tío
the haters of aro and the in short the haters
los haters de aro y al en fin los haters
of aro and the FBI are some
de aro y al fbi son unas cuentas
small accounts dedicated to them who are
pequeñas dedicadas a ellos que se
dedicated to criticizing everything they do the
dedican a criticar todo lo que hacen la
first account that started this
primera cuenta que comenzó este
movement is called pepita or josefa you
movimiento se llama pepita o josefa la
can call her whatever you want not
podéis llamar como queráis no
because of this they call all the
por esto llaman pepita a todos los
haters pepita one day an account don omar today
haters un día a una cuenta don omar hoy
insulting her and she was one of
insultándola y era una de las mayores
Alex's biggest donors her identity was leaked
donadoras de álex se filtró su identidad
because she forgot to donate anonymously for
debido a que olvidó donar en anónimo por
the serious step that
el serio paso eso
or I mean I will
o sea
not do to insult her
yo no haré para insultarla
and she was one of Alex's biggest donors I
y era una de las mayores donadores de
mean she wanted Alex's 10 seconds
o sea quería los 10 segundos de álex
for herself
para ella
and that's why she hates
y por eso odia área
that area she spends a lot of you or I mean I call it
esa pasa mucho de ti o sea yo lo llamo
service
servicio
I call it a gervacio because because it
yo lo llamo un gervacio porque porque
appears without showing its face I feel identity
aparece sin dar la cara siento identidad
for something
por algo
okay for example
vale yo por ejemplo
when I have to tell someone something I
cuando tengo que decirle algo a alguien
tell them from my account it makes me
se lo digo desde mi cuenta a mí me da
very sorry for many people who think
mucha pena muchas personas que se creen
that we don't know or some of us know no
que no lo sabemos o algunos sabemos no
but I don't care and they put in multiple
pero me da igual y se ponen con multi
accounts
cuentas
son motivates
hijo motiva
and sometimes no man sometimes
y a veces no tío a veces personas
quite old people don't say please
bastante mayores no diga por favor
that we have some pellets it's no
que tenemos unos pellet es no
and of course because they don't have balls that's how
y claro porque no tienen [__] así las
things are with their real identity
cosas con su identidad real
in what happens to know
en lo que pasa saber
one day an account donated to roy and
un día una cuenta donó a roy y
insulting her and she was one of the biggest
insultándola y era una de las mayores
don adoration
don adoración
or so she was caught it
o sea que fue la pillada
was the psuv of your channel her name is paula
era el psuv de tu canal se llama paula
torres I
torres
still haven't  has donated to tell me that I
aún no me ha donado para decirme que
hope I'm not interested in someone better who doesn't
ojalá no interesa a alguien mejor que no
deserve me, of
me merece
course that state Paula wanted the 10
claro esa estatal paula quería los 10
seconds of Levy
segundos de levy
yes yes they are very put that to the Afore that happens to them
sí sí son muy poner eso a la afore les
and I enjoy it for a long time I
y disfruto hace mucho
want to see at all God you have not
quiero ver en absoluto dios
put the insult to me Paulo to
no me habéis puesto el insulto paulo a
no note is
no nota
not in the south
no está en el sur
the little breast is
la pechuguita
this
es esta
the mental ones
las mentales
everything everything
todo
some single
todo algún solo
now well the insult to the enemies
ahora bien el insulto a los enemigos
I only need
yo sólo necesito
[Music]
[Música]
shake no no no
agita no
what goes
no no que va
efe we have caught so we believe it
efe hemos pillado tan creemos
was about your channel her name is Paula Torres she
era sobre tu canal se llama paula torres
has not donated to me yet to tell me that I
aún no me ha donado para decirme que
hope you find someone better who doesn't
ojalá encuentres a alguien mejor que no
deserve me but
me merece pero
I know who Pobla Tornesa is well the
yo sé quién es pobla tornesa pues lo
same is our nugget
mismo es nuestra pepita
a little ugly that I used that image
un poco feo que yo utilicé esa imagen
of the coffee without having finished it
del café sin haberlo terminado
hi it seems a little ugly that I used that
hi parece un poco feo que utilice esa
image of the car towards having finished it well well you will
imagen del coche hacia haberlo terminado
see it finished
pues bueno pues ya lo veréis terminado
nothing happens
no pasa nada
friends
amigos
offerings
ofrendas
but Paula is present
pero paula está presente
but yes
pero sí
the looting what a catch
el pillaje
kebir giza
vaya pillada kébir güiza
what a shame
qué vergüenza
[Music]
[Música]
ah or so what do you  it seems okay okay okay he already asked for it he already asked for it he
ah o sea qué te parece vale vale vale ya
asked for it or rather it's
lo pidió ya lo pide lo pidió o sea que
not that you think it's ugly and that it
no es que te parezca fea y que te haya
offended you because I put the image that they have
ofendido porque he puesto la imagen que
n't finished yet
no han terminado todavía
but that it is or what do you think he wants to
sino que está o qué te parece que quiere
finish the game today he's
terminar el juego hoy
right it's true
tiene la razón es verdad
today at the premiere of the creative series
hoy al estrenar la serie del creativo
but we can't see it here I would be I'm going to
pero no la podemos ver aquí estaría voy
put it it is we would
a poner lo es
be going to put it god
estaríamos a ponerlo dios
direct his stream in his live he talks
directo su stream en su directo habla
about certain accounts that have tried to
sobre ciertas cuentas que han intentado
separate them based on axis and on
que se separen a base de eje y en
twitter
twitter
like like how
como como como
carl tries to separate them he pulls out his
carl intenta que se separen tira de
trade let's
oficio
see I'm freaked out because we're already
a ver flipo porque ya estamos
used to this type of people
acostumbrados en este tipo de gente
vila - you and I do review for more
ávila - tú y yo hacemos review para más
increases in chicago something with you today it is
alzas en chicago algo contigo hoy se ve
clearly seen why aro has already stopped
claramente el porqué aro ya dejó de
playing with the fbi playing with people ni
jugar con el fbi jugando con gente ni
hearn and herney and fargas he had 3000 and
hearn y herney y fargas tenía 3000 y
when he entered the fbi they lowered it to
cuando entró al fbi le bajaron hasta
1900 today it is clear why today and every
1900 hoy queda claro porque hoy y cada
day more he signs up to play with farga
día más se apunta a jugar con farga
vegeta and willy
vegeta y willy
carlos delfino man what you have to
carlos delfino tío lo que tienes que
do is learn to write god
hacer es aprender a escribir dios
however now  In his live he says that
sin embargo ahora en su directo dice que
with that constant hey they are achieving the
con ese hey constante están logrando
opposite and that he plans to file a
todo lo contrario y que tiene pensado
complaint. Some complaints are
denunciar algunas
coming, complaints are
se vienen denuncias
coming from damn things.
se vienen de malditas
Yesterday I received them from various parts, from
ayer me han llegado de varias partes de
various places, that lately the hate
varios lugares que últimamente el hate
towards him and me is like, like,
hacia él y hacia mí está como como
rising, not like he's
elevándose no en plan como que se está
climbing to the moon, no, and no, well, there are
subiendo a la luna no y no nos pues nos
people who care about us and
hay gente que se preocupa por nosotros y
tell us, hey, look, lately, such and such,
nos lo dice oye mira últimamente tal
because well, it's about
porque
time I
pues ya estaría ya va siendo hora de que
filed a complaint, it's because I don't know what, because I don't
denuncie es porque no sé qué porque no
know which one,
sé cuál
and I thank god because we have
y yo le doy gracias a dios porque
the filters and we don't find out
tenemos los filtros y no nos enteramos
anything. I always respond the same way, like, they
de nada yo respondo siempre lo mismo en
are people without a [ __ ] life, they are
plan yo son gente sin [__] vida son
children because we have already verified it
niños porque ya lo hemos comprobado
because I hired people to know the
porque yo contraté a personas para saber
whole issue and why all this
todo el tema y porque venía todo éste
hating was coming, and they are [ __ ] children, they are
hating tal y son [__] niños son niños
16 year old children, and the ones who can be the most, you
de 16 años ya los que más se les puede
know what, well, I can't tell you
sabéis qué tío bueno no puedo contar
much, it
mucho
touched him, man, he's stupid but you
le tocado tío es tonto pero te
and you remember that
y os acordáis de
damn guy, you remember that
del maldito ese tío os acordáis del
damn guy who was dedicated to putting my
maldito ese que se dedicaba a poner mi
address and phone number everywhere
dirección y teléfono por todas partes de
internet and accusing me of horrible things
internet y acusándome de cosas horribles
with anonymous accounts and the guy ended up
con cuentas anónimas y acabó el tío
creating a bunch of websites damn I have
creando un montón de páginas web ostia
n't told you and Banesto
no te lo he contado y banesto la semana
next week they're going to well I'm not going to say
que viene me van a bueno no voy a decir
what program but a very famous
qué programa pero un programa muy famoso
TV program you're going to see it on TV okay
de la tele lo vais a ver en la tele vale
and they're going to interview me okay and not
y me ha me van a entrevistar vale y no
only are they going to interview me I'm
solamente me van a entrevistar es que se
forgetting two videos that this employee
me olvida dos vídeos que este empleado
not only are they going to
no solamente es que me vayan a
interview me but they're also going to show
entrevistar sino que además van a poner
how a company is in the program
como una empresa está en el programa
a company that is dedicated to the
participa una empresa que se dedica a la
elimination of all the content and to
eliminación de todo el contenido ya
detect and maybe with that they'll
detectar y a lo mejor con eso van a
move the case more god let's
mover más el caso dios
see if once and for all they put
a ver si de una puñetera vez le meten en
the guy in jail or something god
la cárcel al pavo o algo dios
or I mean for now the good thing is that it seems that
o sea de momento lo bueno es que va que
we're going to get all the
vamos a conseguir que se elimine todo el
[ __ ] content eliminated finally it was going to so from
[__] contenido por fin iba así que de
here until Tuesday when they come to my
aquí al martes que cuando vienen a mi
house we have to look it's that we are
casa hay que buscar es que estamos
clues as to whether there is still something out there I
pistas sobre si hay algo todavía por ahí
think that website that they
que creo que la página web esa que
paid for that must have spent the money is
pagaron que se tuvo de gastar la pasta
worth it, well, it triumphed well the triumph
vale el bien triunfó bueno el triunfo
crisis of triumphing no  the guy
crisis de triunfar no triunfado el tío
is free but I see that stopping me I only
está libre pero eso lo veo parar yo sólo
see for jail he is objectively those
veo para cárcel está objetivamente esos
jail
cárcel
objectively that is for jail Alexa
objetivamente eso es para cárcel alexa
I have figure background music since you don't
tengo figura música de fondo ya que no
want music as soon as I invite the
queréis música en cuanto invite a los
clips at least a lot of here
clips por lo menos mucho de aquí
and they go the other day I reported a ball
y van yo el otro día reporte un cojón
of things also there
también de cosas
are many things still on the
hay muchas cosas todavía en la página
website we do not have the view they have
web no tenemos la vista
come to me from various parts from
me han llegado de varias partes de
various places that lately the hate
varios lugares que últimamente al hate
towards the cold towards me it is like
hacia el frío hacia mí está como como
rising not in a way like it is
elevándose no en plan como que se está
climbing to the moon
subiendo a la luna
because there are no people who care about
pues no hay gente que se preocupa por
us and tell us hey look
nosotros y nos lo dice oye mira
lately such because
últimamente tal porque
well it would be time for me to
pues ya estaría ya va siendo hora de que
report it is because I do not know what because I do not
denuncie es porque no sé qué porque no
know which and I
sé cuál
thank god because we have
y yo le doy gracias a dios porque
the filters and we do not find out
tenemos los filtros y no nos enteramos
anything I always respond the same like I
de nada yo respondo siempre lo mismo en
am people without a [ __ ] life they are
plan yo son gente sin [__] vida son
children because we have already verified it
niños porque ya lo hemos comprobado
because I hired people to know the
porque yo contraté a personas para saber
whole subject and why all this
todo el tema y porque venía todo éste
hating such and these children are
hating tal y son estos niños son niños
16 year old children who can
de 16 años a los que más se les puede
lose their hair the most is their parents you know already  if they
caer el pelo es a sus padres sabes ya se
tell their parents and
les diga a sus padres y probablemente
their parents are probably the ones who will be left
sus padres son los que se queden en la
[ __ ] broke trying to pay such
[__] ruina por intentar pagar una
huge compensation, so yes I know if
indemnización tremenda así sí sé si sale
the complaint comes out blank
la denuncia en blanco
if we want you know then the
si queremos sabes entonces
intention today is to talk a little for
intención hoy es hablar un poquito para
you for the people this is [ __ ]
vosotros para la gente está que [__]
going little Motrin that Gael note
iba poco motrin que gael nota
wow
guau
how they catch the turkey and tell me my
como trinquen a el pavo y me diga mi
lawyer forward
abogado de palante
this has to be compensation from
esto tiene que ser una indemnización de
justice if I'm not saying it for profit
la justicia si no lo digo por lucrar
but because it has to be
sino porque tiene que serlo
okay old old table okay we prepare
vale vieja vieja mesa vale preparamos
nothing let's see it's not processed it didn't
nada a ver es que no se procesa no
transcend it was turned off a long time ago
trascendía se apagó hace mucho tiempo
let's try centrals now okay
vamos a intentar centrales ahora vale
between
entre
Armando in stratum 2 I
armando en el estrato 2
just made a nut
acabo de chufa
nothing that is ruining his entire life not
nada eso es arruinarle la vida entera no
ruining him he has ruined us it is ruining nobody's
arruinarle nos ha arruinado es la ruina
life Alexa
la vida nadie alexa
Alexa is connecting to the internet the king
alexa se está conectando internet el rey
is in a mouse in the light old age open
es en un ratón a la luz edad oberta
head I don't know if they will have it of course it
cabeza no sé si tendrán desde luego
seems not but I'm going to try to
parece ser que no pero voy a intentar
be as polite and as calm
ser lo más educada y lo más tranquila
as possible with you inside that I
posible con vosotros dentro de que
try to understand that you are not right in
intento comprender que no estáis bien de
the head and I try to understand and  I'm not
la cabeza y lo intento comprender y no
trying woman at all with that
me intento mujer en absoluto con eso
inside of that I'm going to try to make you a
dentro de eso voy a intentar haceros un
little sketch okay and I don't know if you realize
pequeño croquis vale y no sé si es que
or see
os dais con os dais cuenta o a ver a
Alexa
alexa
put on a playlist
pon una play list
without copyright here you have one of the
sin copyright aquí tienes una de las
most listened to laws in Latin America on Amazon
leyes más escuchadas latino en amazon
Music no no no no Alexa for Alexa
music no no no no alexa para alexa
a playlist without copyright
una playlist sin copyright
here you have one of the most
aquí tienes una de las playlists más
listened to playlists the best news on
escuchadas las mejores novedades en
Amazon Music
amazon music
Alexa for
alexa para
playlist without copyright
play list sin copyright
Alexa
alexa
music without copyright
música sin copyright
[Music]
[Música]
these will be 5 wright
estas serán 5 wright
this can be without copyright family
esta puede ser sin copyright familiar
or anything
ni de coña
Alexa for
alexa para
[Music] we
[Música]
have to change the name of the exam
hay que cambiarle el nombre al examen
because if I don't understand all your
porque si no entiendo todas vuestras
Alex as and how do we name it
álex as y cómo le ponemos de nombre
how do we name it
como le ponemos de nombre
how could we call it
como la podríamos llamar
Paula we call it Paulo
paula le ponemos paulo
Alexa I want to change the name
alexa quiero cambiarse el nombre
to do it you will have within the
para hacerlo tendrá dentro de la sección
configuration section and click on the
configuración y haz clic en la
configure all that what you want to do
configurar todo eso lo que quieras hacer
the change add vouchers
el cambio agrega vales
d it is
d
supposed to have an application on the
se supone que tenga una aplicación en el
mobile that for him is healthy it
móvil que para él es sana
is supposed that they had
se supone que tenían aplicaciones
mobile applications to valera
móviles a valera
what will be the mobile alert application
cuál será la aplicación de alerta del
or flight
móvil o vuelo
to  alex
a álex
settings
configuración
notifications privacy voice replies
notificaciones privacidad respuestas de
account settings
configuración de cuenta configuración de
device settings alexa settings
dispositivos configuración de alexa
voice replies voice reply
respuestas de voz respuesta de voz
as short reply famous personality i
a modo de respuesta breve personalidad
don't know the truth
no sé la verdad
alexa open white noise
alexa abre ruido blanco
ok here are sleep sounds
vale aquí tiene sonidos para dormir
white noise
ruido blanco
alexa stop
alexa para
or are you aware that who you are
o sois conscientes de que a quién estáis
attacking
atacando
are two people who live together ok we
son dos personas que viven juntas vale
already live together we are together all day
ya vivimos juntos estamos todo el día
in fact we are two
juntos de hecho somos dos personas
homebodies we work in the same field
caseras trabajamos de lo mismo con lo
which gives us the advantage of seeing each other
cual tenemos la ventaja de que nos vemos
more than any other
más que cualquier pareja en general
normal couple we are at
normal y corriente estamos todo el día
home together all day but pere but
en casa juntos pero pere pero
[Music]
[Música]
ok
vale
edit name
editar nombre
name can't be changed you
no se le puede cambiar de nombre se le
can call alex amazon done I
puede llamar álex a amazon hecho
can put done if you want let's see I
le puedo poner hecho si queréis a ver
can put done if you want but
le puedo poner hecho si queréis pero es
with that it activates a lot he said
que con ello se activa muchísimo dijo
with facts to rough
con hechos a basto
and with that I can say it many times I have done done I have
y con eso lo puedo decir yo muchas veces
today I have not done my homework sorry I do
hoy no he hecho los deberes
n't know
lo siento eso no lo sé
echo
eco
but the one that is empty
pero el que está vacío
the milk is less likely that I say
la leche es menos probable que yo diga
extra salt without meaning to I do
sal extra sin quererlo
n't know if you have noticed okay but
no sé si os habéis dado cuenta vale pero
we are both together all day  and we talk and
estamos todo el día los dos y hablamos y
we are together and of course if suddenly I
estamos juntos y claro si de repente me
get a message from a person saying
llega un mensaje de una persona diciendo
that at x moment I am with another
que yo en equis momento estoy con otra
person and at that moment I am with Alex
persona y en ese momento estoy con álex
or I am talking to Alex on the phone,
o estoy hablando con alex por teléfono
well man, your credibility
pues hombre vuestra credibilidad
of this that would be normal stays
de esto que sería lo normal se queda
here and everything else that you say
aquí y todo lo demás que digáis no os va
nobody is going to believe you, do you understand me, I mean
a creer nadie me entendéis o sea no os
nobody is going to believe you anything and much more
va a creer nadie nada y mucho más
knowing that on top of our
sabiendo que encima a raíz de nuestro
behavior we are in
comportamiento nosotros estamos en
constant communication not only between the
constante comunicación ya no solo entre
two of us but with the rest of the
nosotros dos sino con el resto de
people followers people close to us we
personas seguidores personas cercanas ya
are already talking all day long yes with
estamos todo el día hablando que sí con
friends about this subject yes with
los amigos de este tema que sí con
friends yes with close people yes
amigos que sí con gente cercana que sí
with followers and if you notice
con seguidores y si os dais cuenta
if you notice the fact that
si os dais cuenta el hecho de que
we have more communication than
nosotros tengamos más comunicación de lo
normal also means that we do
normal también hace que nosotros
not have any problems, I mean,
luego no tengamos ningún problema o sea
obviously I see that someone is attacking
yo evidentemente veo que alguien ataca a
Alex
álex
and me as a normal person who loves him
y a mí como persona normal que quiere al
the only thing that is going to provoke me is that I
es lo único que me va a provocar es que
want to protect him more and Alex the same way
quiera protegerle más y álex igual así
if Alex sees that I am also being attacked the
si álex ve también me están atacando lo
only thing that is born from him is wanting to
único que le nace de él es querer
protect me more then you are
protegerme más entonces estáis
achieving just the opposite which is
consiguiendo justo lo contrario que es
uniting a couple more than separating them I don't
unir más a una pareja que separarla no
know if you really realize then I do
sé si os dais cuenta de verdad entonces
n't know are you like
no sé usted es como
me always the
yo siempre
same because it's that really
igual porque es que realmente sea
while someone is inventing type
mientras alguien se está inventando tipo
no because it's that she leaves she's not
no porque es que a ella se va no esté
where okay she leaves I don't know where and I don't know
donde vale que se va no sé dónde y no sé
what we are both together then she
qué estamos los dos juntos entonces
loses credibility and it
pierde como credibilidad y
's absurd and we are never going
es que es absurdo y nosotros nunca vamos
to allow the other person to be
a permitir que a la otra persona le
hurt you know if we are in constant
hagan daño sabe si estamos en constante
communication s a I do
comunicación s a
n't know if you have realized maybe
no sé si os habéis dado cuenta quizá
this same thing that you are doing works
esto mismo que estáis haciendo funcione
for separated couples like that
para parejas separadas en plan que vive
each one lives on its own
cada una en un lado
but it doesn't exist for us
pero no existe para nosotros
whether they like it is what they wanted this
ya le guste es lo que querían que esta
attention no no no no no it's not that it's not that they are
atención no no no no no es que no es que
looking for what they are looking for is attention on
busquen a lo que buscan es atención por
twitter why why why are they
twitter por qué por qué por qué se
bored what they are looking for is attention on
aburren lo que buscan es atención por
twitter because they are bored but who they
twitter porque se aburren pero a quien
hate is Alex or me so how do they
odian es a álex oa mí entonces como
want to hurt Alex the only thing they
quieren hacer daño a álex lo único que
achieve is that Alex and I are the
consiguen es que álex y yo los más
closest the only thing I want to emphasize is
unidos lo único que quiero recalcar es
envy what they have  a mix of
envidia lo que tienen es una mezcla de
a lot of things but what a bpd site I
un montón de cosas pero qué sitio bpd
had as such how bad it is and there are
tuve como tal como está de mal y está la
people wanting to break up a couple
gente queriendo que se separe una pareja
with whom they have nothing to do with
con la que no tienen nada que ver con
a couple that doesn't affect them at all in their
una pareja que no les afecta nada en sus
lives
vidas
however now in their live and desire to
sin embargo ahora en su directo y deseo
be constant they are achieving the
de ser constante están logrando todo lo
opposite and that they plan to report
contrario y que tiene pensado denunciar
some or
alguna
other, that is, the overlay no,
o sea el overlay no
the overlay no right,
el overlay no verdad
the overlay no but this here yes,
el overlay no pero esto aquí sí
the overlay I don't see it could be
el overlay no me la vez podría ser
but here yes you
pero aquí sí
have to go through or you don't have to
hay que pasar o no
go through a year ago
hay que pasar un año atrás
[Music]
[Música]
ah
ah